ieplads.com 2008-12-16

# Jeevansathi Matrimonials- Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

Jeevansathi.com is a division of Info Edge (I) Ltd. It is an online matrimonial portal endeavoring constantly to provide you with premium matrimonial services. Since we are strongly committed to your right to privacy, we have drawn have a privacy statement in place with regard to the information we collect from you. 

We use a secure server for credit card transactions to protect the credit card information of our clients and Cookies are used to store the login information. 

1\. 

**What information does Jeevansathi.com collect from you?**   
We gather information from members and guests who apply for the various services our site offers. It includes, but may not be limited to, email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, e-mail Id, mailing address, zip code and telephone number or fax number.

2\. 

**How Jeevansathi.com uses the information it collects/tracks?**   
We collect information from our clients primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver personalized experience.

3\. 

**With whom the site shares the information it collects/tracks?**   
The information collected from any of our clients is not shared with any individual or organization without the former’s approval. Jeevansathi.com does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security. We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer. 

4\. 

**When and to whom is my contact information disclosed?**   
When you accept a paid member or if you are a paid member and accept another member's contact or if you are a paid member and initiate a contact with another member, your contact details will be disclosed to the other member you have accepted or initiated contact with. 

5\. 

**Do all visitors have to pay?**   
NO, All visitors to our site may browse the site, search the ads and view any articles or features our site has to offer without entering any personal information or paying money. 

6\. 

**Can users contact any number of profiles in a single day?**   
As a paid member of this site, you have the privilege to contact lots of profiles. However, there is a specified limit to 100 contacts for security reasons per day. If you want to contact more profiles than the specified limit in a single day, he/she can do so after the completion of 24 hours of their login time. 

**Notice:** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments or as a result of a change of policy in our company. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please write in to webmaster@jeevansathi.com
